Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Blueprints, plans, drawings, photos, renderings, and other material
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Residence B by FLW Hollywood, 1920 (Box 660)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 660
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Residence units E, F, G by FLW Hollywood, no date (Box 658)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 658
  - Oliver, Lela - Residence Chevy Chase, Glendale, 1926; Project No. 30 (Box 166, Box 343)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 343
  - Olmstead, Marion - Residence No address, no date (Box 640)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 640
  - Othman - Metal roof residence 2200 Broadview Terrace, 1940; Project No. 129 (Box 155, Box 424)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 424
  - Owens, L.D. - Store Hollywood, 1930; Project No. 65 (Box 366)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 366
  - Pent-o-Rama (Pedicini) - Residence Eureka Dr., Holmby Hills, 1956; Project No. 251 (Box 255, Box 531)
    Blueprints: Box 255
    Plans/Drawings: Box 531
  - Pent-o-Rama - Residence Arbolando Road, Santa Barbara, 1955; Project No. 242 (Box 172, Box 525, Box 646)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 525
  - Pheiffer, John F. & Hulet, Dr. William - Residence Granada Blvd., Coral Gables, Florida, 1963; Project No. 308 (Box 259, Box 260, Box 192, Box 565)
    Blueprints: Boxes 259, 260, 192
    Plans/Drawings: Box 565
  - Phi Kappa Sigma - Fraternity house No address, no date (Box 679)
  - Phoenix Country Club - Landscaping Phoenix, Arizona, 1920 May; Project No. 1 (Box 636)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 636
  - Phoenix Country Club - Phoenix Country Club Phoenix, Arizona, 1920; Project No. 1 (Box 106)
    Blueprints: Box 106
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor (Herman Steiner) - Entrance gate 400 S. Bundy, Beverly Hills, 1962; Project No. 298 (Box 237)
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor (Herman Steiner) - Guest house remodel 400 S. Bundy, Los Angeles, 1965; Project No. 322 (Box 267, Box 573)
    Blueprints: Box 267
    Plans/Drawings: Box 573
  - Piatigorsky, Gregor (Herman Steiner) - Remodel & addition 400 S. Bundy Dr., Beverly Hills, 1952; Project No. 275 (Box 252, Box 544)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 544
  - Pico Robertson Mall - Urban planning Los Angeles, 1961; Project No. 292 (Box 232, Box 559)
    Blueprints: Box 232
    Plans/Drawings: Box 559
  - Pico-Robertson Mall - Exhibit pasteup Los Angeles, 1961 (Box 645)
  - Pihl, Charles - Residence & garage Parkwood Knolls, Edina, Minn., 1960; Project No. 288 (Box 203, Box 553)
    Blueprints: Box 203
    Plans/Drawings: Box 553
  - Pihl, Charles - Residence Park Wood Knolls, Edina, Minn., 1960; Project No. 298 (Box 671)
  - Pilgrimage Play Theatre - Remodel for music concerts - perspective Los Angeles, no date (Box 119)
  - Pilgrimage Play Theatre - Remodel for music concerts Los Angeles, 1961; Project No. 293 (Box 271, Box 557)
    Blueprints: Box 271
    Plans/Drawings: Box 557
  - Pole, Rupert - Residence & beach house Los Angeles, 1957; Project No. 264 (Box 523)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 523
  - Pole, Rupert - Residence furniture Los Angeles, 1962 July (Box 117)
    Blueprints: Box 117
  - Pole, Rupert - Residence [beach house] Los Angeles, 1957; Project No. 260 (Box 145)
  - Polster, Leonard - Residence 1098 Hilcrest Rd., Beverly Hills, 1957; Project No. 260 (Box 200, Box 222, Box 521, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Box 200, 222
    Plans/Drawings: Box 521
  - Pope-Leighey - Studio and driveway resiting No address, 1971 (Box 269, Box 665)
    Blueprints: Box 269
    Plans/Drawings: Box 665
  - Powell, L.H. - Residence 9107 St. Ives Dr., 1948; Project No. 180 (Box 150, Box 471)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 471
  - Powell, L.H. - Residences (4) & garages 9101 St. Ives Dr., 1948; Project No. 179 (Box 122, Box 470)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 470
  - Prescott - [Untitled] Block print, no date (Box 645)
  - Preuss, Kenneth - Landscaping Laughlin Park, Hollywood, 1921; Project No. 3 (Box 238, Box 632)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 632
  - Price, Tony & Barbieri, Gladys - Book shop remodel No address, 1934; Project No. 80 (Box 217, Box 391)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 391
  - Professional building Yucca & Vine, Hollywood, 1930; Project No. 60 (Box 355)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 355
  - Ramona Gardens - Housing project Los Angeles, 1943; Project No. 141 (Box 449)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 449
  - Record Co. - Sketches No address, no date (Box 294)
  - Redlich, Mr. & Mrs. Ivo P. - Residence, landscape & garage 602 N. Arden, Beverly Hills, 1946; Project No. 168 (Box 123, Box 459, Box 673)
    Blueprints: Box 123
    Plans/Drawings: Box 459
  - Reitz, Henry - Residence Beverly Glen & Charing Rd., 1947; Project No. 173 (Box 270, Box 462)
    Blueprints: Box 270
    Plans/Drawings: Box 462
  - Richardson, Burt - Residence 1849 Campus Rd., Eagle Rock, 1932; Project No. 71 (Box 159, Box 373)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 373
  - Riverside Portland Cement Co. - Barracks no address, no date (Box 640)
  - Road sign no. 11 No address, no date (Box 646)
  - Robins, Herbert - Residence - architect: Van Pelt Beverly Hills, 1928; Project No. 48 (Box 208, Box 220)
    Blueprints: Box 208, 220
  - Robinson, Louis, Dr. & Mrs. - Residence #2 Comstock Ave., 1941; Project No. 139 (Box 204, Box 434)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 434
  - Rosenman, M.H. - Lloyd Wright Photo, 1963 (Box 672)
  - Rosenwald Foundation - School house by FLW Tennessee, no date (Box 661)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 661
  - Ruby, Harry - Residence 805 N. Rodeo Rd., Beverly Hills, 1937; Project No. 104 (Box 137, Box 406)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 406
  - Saint Luke's Presbyterian Church - Church 26825 Rolling Hills Rd., Rolling Hills Estates, 1958; Project No. 273 (Box 243, Box 263, Box 264, Box 542, Box 546)
    Blueprints: Boxes 243, 263, 264
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 542, 546
  - Saint Luke's Presbyterian Church - Study for Kirk House, first unit of St. Luke's 26825 Rolling Hills Road, Rolling Hills Estates, 1958; Project No. 273 (Box 669)
  - Samuel, Louis 5609 Valley Oak Dr., 1931; Project No. 50A
    SEE: Navarro, Ramon - Samuel House addition
  - Samuel, Louis - Residence Glendower Dr., Los Angeles, 1962; Project No. 299 (Box 268, Box 552)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 552
  - Samuel, Louis - Residence Glendower Dr., Los Angeles, 1962; Project No. 301 (Box 668)
  - Samuel, Louis - Residence 5609 Valley Oak Drive, 1928; Project No. 50 (Box 230, Box 352)
    Blueprints: Box 230
    Plans/Drawings: Box 352
  - Samuel, Mrs. Louis - Residence 579 N. Bundy Dr., 1934; Project No. 84 (Box 248, Box 387)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 387
  - San Marcos in the Desert - Desert resort near Chandler, Arizona, 1927; Project No. 19 (Box 270)
  - Santa Monica High School - Theatre & planting Santa Monica, Calif., 1922; Project No. 6 (Box 174, Box 634)
    Blueprints: Box 174
    Plans/Drawings: Box 634
  - Sauer, W.E. - Residence 6309 MacPherson, St. Louis, Missouri, 1935; Project No. 90 (Box 382)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 382
  - Schuyler, Janet Allen - Residence 2770 Club Dr., 1944; Project No. 146 (Box 446)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 446
  - Schwein, L.N. - Remodel R. Griffith ranch house for new owner 4965 Rigoletto St., Canoga Park, 1951; Project No. 205 (Box 111, Box 492)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 492
  - Seeberger, Louis - Residence & garage remodel 4461 Van Alden, Tarzana, 1961; Project No. 295 (Box 287, Box 291, Box 556)
    Blueprints: Boxes 287, 291
    Plans/Drawings: Box 556
  - Seletz - Residence No address, 1956; Project No. 249 (Box 280, Box 527)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 527
  - Shulman, H. - Residence & carport 211 Glenroy Place, Los Angeles, 1950; Project No. 203 (Box 193, Box 490)
    Blueprints: Box 193
    Plans/Drawings: Box 490
  - Shulman, H. - Residence additions 211 Glenroy Place, 1952; Project No. 218 (Box 112)
    Blueprints: Box 112
  - Sierra Madre - Landscaping of city park competition Sierra Madre, Calif., 1923; Project No. 13 (Box 633)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 633
  - Slater, Mrs. Frank T. - Residence Hiatt St., La Habra, 1951; Project No. 210 (Box 110, Box 516, Box 646)
    Blueprints: Box 110
    Plans/Drawings: Box 516
  - Smith, Mr. & Mrs. Mel - Residence & garage 3146 Haddington Dr., 1945; Project No. 151 (Box 135, Box 438)
    Blueprints: Box 135
    Plans/Drawings: Box 438
  - Smith, S.R. - Residence Chevy Chase, 1935; Project No. 88 (Box 142, Box 384)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 384
  - Smith, Walter - Residence No address, 1946; Project No. 166 (Box 457)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 457
  - Smith, Warren C. - Residence Los Angeles, 1944; Project No. 145 (Box 413)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 413
  - Smith, William - Residence 7346 N. Alta Vista, 1939; Project No. 115 (Box 223, Box 412, Box 702)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 412
    Other: Box 702
  - Solar Farms Apple Valley, Calif., 1965-1975
    SEE: Lair, Max
  - Soloman, Solie - Nursery School, Hill & Dale 16706 Marquez Ave., Pacific Palisades, 1949; Project No. 188 (Box 236, Box 137, Box 476)
    Blueprints: Boxes 236, 137
    Plans/Drawings: Box 476
  - Solomon, Solie - Play house, vehicle storage, flag pole 16706 Marquez Ave., Pacific Palisades, 1951; Project No. 209 (Box 479)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 479
  - Sowden, John - Residence 5121 Franklin Ave., 1926; Project No. 34 (Box 125, Box 222, Box 263, Box 338, Box 677, Box 673)
    Blueprints: Boxes 125, 222, 263
    Plans/Drawings: Box 338
    Photos: Box 677, 673
  - Speaker resonator 858 N. Doheny Dr., Beverly Hills, 1956; Project No. 247 (Box 258, Box 528)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 528
  - Springtime in Texas by Prof. A. de Tanden Print, no date (Box 645)
  - St. Marks Tower - Apartment building The Bowery, New York, 1930; Project No. 63 (Box 143, Box 179)
    Blueprints: Boxes 143, 179
  - Stahl, John - Residence Beverly Hills, 1925; Project No. 24 (Box 612)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 612
  - Stained glass window Design, no date (Box 644)
  - Stein, Mr. & Mrs. Ronald - Residence - preliminaries Granada Hills, Calif., 1959; Project No. 273.5 (Box 205)
  - Stein, Roland - Residence No address, 1960; Project No. 284 (Box 177, Box 551)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 551
  - Steiner, Herman. Beverly Hills, 1952-1962
    SEE: Piatigorsky, Gregor
  - Steiner, Herman - Chess Club remodel 8801 Cashio St., Los Angeles, 1961; Project No. 291 (Box 276, Box 558)
    Blueprints: Box 276
    Plans/Drawings: Box 558
  - Steiner, Herman - Chess Club remodel 1499 S. Robertson, 1961, 1962; Project No. 302 (Box 555)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 555
  - Stendahl, Earl - Candy factory, & remodel estimates, addition, gallery 710 Victory Blvd., Burbank, 1946; Project No. 160 (Box 244, Box 451)
    Blueprints: Box 244
    Plans/Drawings: Box 451
  - Stendahl, Earl - Residence 7055 Hillside, Los Angles, 1941; Project No. 131 (Box 421)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 421
  - Stendahl, Earl - Residence no address, 1944; Project No. 145 (Box 252)
  - Storer, Dr. - Residence - designed by FLW 8061 Hollywood Blvd., 1923; Project No. 17 (Box 679)
  - Swann, Harold - Residence Canon Dr., Hope Ranch, Santa Barbara, 1940; Project No. 122 (Box 430)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 430
  - Swartz, Harold - Sculpture monument to picture industry & studio Hollywood, 1930; Project No. 64 (Box 154, Box 367)
    Blueprints: Box 154
    Plans/Drawings: Box 367
  - Swedenborg Memorial Chapel - Campanile & berm walls - second unit Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, 1953, 1954; Project No. 229 (Box 132)
    Blueprints: Box 132
  - Swedenborg Memorial Chapel - Chapel superstructure - first unit, prelims Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, 1949; Project No. 199,199A (Box 113, Box 641)
    Blueprints: Box 113
    Plans/Drawings: Box 641
  - Swedenborg Memorial Chapel - Chapel superstructure - first unit Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, 1949; Project No. 199 (Box 181, Box 191, Box 300)
    Blueprints: Boxes 181, 191, 300
  - Swedenborg Memorial Chapel - Diorama Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, 1970; Project No. 341 (Box 245)
    Blueprints: Box 245
  - Swedenborg Memorial Chapel - Glass loggia Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, 1977; Project No. 362 (Box 295, Box 296, Box 300)
    Blueprints: Boxes 295, 296, 300
  - Swedenborg Memorial Chapel - Wayfarer's Chapel Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, no date (Box 671, Box 675)
    Photos: Boxes 671, 675
  - Taggart, Martha - Residence additions & alterations 5423 Black Oak Drive, 1922, 1924; Project No. 7 (Box 109, Box 333, Box 678)
    Blueprints: Box 109
    Plans/Drawing: Box 333
    Other: Box 678
  - Thanksgiving Square - Civic park Dallas, Texas, 1970; Project No. 345 (Box 243, Box 597)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 597
  - Theta Chi Fraternity - Fraternity house Westwood (UCLA), 1936; Project No. 96 (Box 399, Box 644)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 399
  - Thrifty Drug Store - Drug store Springdale & Warren, Huntington Beach, 1968; Project No. no 320 (Box 220, Box 692)
    Blueprints: Box 220
    Plans/Drawings: Box 692
  - Tibbett, Lawrence - Residence 933 Rexford Dr., Los Angeles, 1930; Project No. 58 (Box 368)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 368
  - Tibbett, Mrs. Grace - Homestead Bakersfield, Calif., 1941; Project No. 134 (Box 249, Box 432)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 432
  - Tibbett, Mrs. Grace - Residence - alterations 5250 Louise Ave., Encino, Calif., 1940; Project No. 120 (Box 431)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 431
  - Tibbett, Mrs. Grace - Residence alterations 5250 Louise Ave., Encino, Calif., 1940; Project No. 125 (Box 245)
  - Tibbett, Mrs. Jane - House sketch Florida, 1947; Project No. 174 (Box 463)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 463
  - Tomer, George - Residence - preliminary drawings 16321 Kinzie St., Sepulveda, Calif., 1973; Project No. 350 (Box 277, Box 600)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 600
  - Tourtellotte, W.B. - Residence 856 S. Berendo, Los Angeles, 1944; Project No. 144 (Box 447, Box 669)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 447
  - Triangle Park - shopping center & remodel Carson & Bellflower, Long Beach, 1969-1970; Project No. 336 (Box 261, Box 581)
    Blueprints: Box 261
    Plans/Drawings: Box 581
  - True, Ellen - Rookery tent Palm Springs, Calif., 1924; Project No. 18 (Box 330)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 330
  - Tule Mat House - Desert Mat House Imperial Highway, 1933; Project No. 79 (Box 156, Box 392)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 392
  - Turtelotte, W.D. Los Angeles, 1944
    SEE: Tourtellotte, W.B.
  - Unidentified - Various No address, no date (Box 537, Box 604, Box 655, Box 643)
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 537, 604, 655
  - Unity Temple - Restoration Oak Park, Illinois, 1973; Project No. 351 (Box 592)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 592
  - University Club - Landscaping Los Angeles, 1922; Project No. 5 (Box 237, Box 635)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 635
  - University of California, Santa Barbara - Exhibit Monograph cover, no date (Box 644)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara - Lloyd Wright exhibit 400 San Marcos Rd., 1967; Project No. 326 (Box 106, Box 111, Box 607)
    Blueprints: Boxes 106, 111
    Plans/Drawings: Box 607
  - Untitled - [unidentified artist] Collage, no date (Box 668)
  - Upham, Frank H. - Landscaping Mendocino Road, Altadena, Calif., 1920; Project No. 2 (Box 149, Box 629)
    Blueprints: Box 149
    Plans/Drawings: Box 629
  - Upham, Mr. & Mrs. F.H. - Residence additions 1943 Mendocino Dr., Altadena, Calif., 1928; Project No. 46 (Box 146)
  - Vidor, Charles - Residence Briercrest Dr. & Alto Credo Dr., 1938; Project No. 111 (Box 211, Box 411)
    Blueprints: Box 211
    Plans/Drawings: Box 411
  - Wagner, G.P. - Residence Filliorium Corp, Palos Verdes, 1953; Project No. 232 (Box 266, Box 520)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 520
  - Watkins, Ray - Motel Newport Beach, 1955; Project No. 363 (Box 292)
    Blueprints: Box 292
  - Wayfarer's Chapel Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, 1949-1977
    SEE: Swedenborg Memorial Chapel
  - Weber, E.J. - Residence 3923 W. 9th St., Los Angeles, 1921; Project No. 4 (Box 332, Box 644)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 332
  - Welton, J. - Additions 859 N. Wilcox, Los Angeles, 1949; Project No. 192 (Box 198, Box 199, Box 200, Box 216)
    Blueprints: Boxes 198, 199, 200, 216
  - Welton, James - Remodel 970 Bel Air Rd., Los Angeles, 1968; Project No. 335 (Box 583)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 583
  - Westfair Shopping Center - Service station Huntington Beach, Calif., 1968; Project No. 330 (Box 579)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 579
  - Westfair Shopping Center - Shopping Center Huntington Beach, Calif., 1968; Project No. 330 (Box 195, Box 226, Box 288, Box 582, Box 576, Box 577, Box 578)
    Blueprints: Boxes 195, 226, 288
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 582, 576, 577, 578
  - Westlake Medical Building 676 Westlake Ave., Los Angeles, 1835; Project No. 87 (Box 131)
    Blueprints: Box 131
  - Wilkes - Theatre & shops Hollywood, 1927; Project No. 41 (Box 235, Box 363)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 363
  - Wilson, Stroh - Wilson College Drive School No address, 1956 (Box 326)
    Blueprints: Box 326
  - Wood, Beatrice - Residence Ojai, Calif., 1949; Project No. 192 (Box 468)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 468
  - World Folk Park - Folk Fair Burbank, Calif., 1964; Project No. 313 (Box 187)
    Blueprints: Box 187
  - World of Frank Lloyd Wright Japanese exhibit poster, no date (Box 666)
  - Wright, Cathryn L. - Urn Sketch, 1959; Project No. 365 (Box 155, Box 618)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 618
  - Wright, David L. - Addition & remodel Phoenix, Arizona, 1965; Project No. 319 (Box 148, Box 177, Box 569)
    Blueprints: Boxes 148, 177
    Plans/Drawings: Box 569
  - Wright, David L. - Residence addition Phoenix, Arizona, 1977; Project No. 358 (Box 148)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd - Additions No address, 1966 (Box 246)
    Blueprints: Box 246
  - Wright, Gibby L. - Residence 5226 E. Exeter Blvd., Phoenix, Arizona, 1967; Project No. 328 (Box 121, Box 575)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 575
  - Wright, Lloyd - [Palm Springs] Abstract study for mural, no date (Box 646)
  - Wright, Lloyd - Architect's studio & residence 858 N. Doheny Dr., Los Angeles, 1927; Project No. 37 (Box 246, Box 677, Box 675, Box 680)
    Photos: Boxes 675, 677, 680
  - Wright, Lloyd - Oasis Hotel, Mt. Baldy Woodblock print, no date (Box 645)
  - Wright, Lloyd - Santa Ynez Mission watercolor, no date (Box 645)
  - Wright, Lloyd - [Untitled] Sketch of nude figure, no date (Box 645)
  - Wright, Robert L. - Residence & landscaping Deepwell Rd., Bethesda, Md., 1960; Project No. 306 (Box 282, Box 562)
    Blueprints: Box 282
    Plans/Drawings: Box 562
  - Wyle, Frank & Edith - Subdivision & landscaping Mulholland Dr., Los Angeles, 1946; Project No. 161 (Box 250, Box 450)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 450
  - Zeitlin & VerBrugge Calendar, 1969 (Box 644)
  - Zeitlin, Jake - Book shop 705-1/2 W. 6th St.,Los Angeles, 1930; Project No. 62 (Box 615, Box 674)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 615